BENJAMIN DELTENRE WEB DEVELOPER

- benjdelt@gmail.com
- benjdelt.github.io/
- **6** 604-762-5243
- **♀** Vancouver BC
- in benidelt
- O benjdelt

Skills

LANGUAGES

JavaScript

Python

Ruby

HTML

CSS

_

TOOLS & LIBRARIES

Node.js

Express

React

Django

JQuery

Ruby on Rails

Flask

Bootstrap

Sass

PostgreSQL

MySQL

MongoDB

July

2018

2007

to

Git

Education

Oct. 2018	Development
Sept.	IEPSCF Ath-
2004	Flobecq
to	Bachelor
Sept.	Accounting

Lighthouse

Diploma Web

Labs

Summary

Full Stack Web Developer with experience in **React, Python and Django**. I have a passion for building apps and creative problem solving. I bring a strong focus to details and good time management skills from my **6 years of experience** in the government finance sector. Fluent in English and French. Legally entitled to work in Canada.

Experience

Freelance Vancouver, BC Web Developer Apr. 2019 to Current

TalentMarketplace:

- Tech stack: Django, React, Redux, PostgreSQL
- Collaborated on a specific project with a senior developer
- Improved Responsive UI based on prototypes
- Integrated new front-end functionalities on a large existing codebase

Shuup Vancouver, BC Developer Intern Feb. 2019 to Mar. 2019

Multi Vendor Marketplace Platform and Custom Development Services

Tech Stack: Python, Django, JavaScript, React, MySQL

- Participated in Open Source development to add features and fix issues
- **Developed** features taking advantage of Django's application system
- Managed ticket progress through Jira following a 2 week sprint agile environment
- Wrote user documentation

TalentMarketplace

Volunteer Web Developer

Vancouver, BC Oct. 2018 to Feb. 2019

TalentMarketplace is an online, project professional recruitment platform.

- Tech stack: Django, React, Redux, PostgreSQL
- Utilized Git source control through Bitbucket repository to pull, branch, push code and create pull requests
- Managed ticket progress through backlog in an Agile sprint development environment
- Robustly **resolved bugs and implemented features** on an existing, enterprise code base to quickly deliver system enhancements that **reached thousands of users**
- Thoroughly QAed (white box tested) all code to have a ticket return rate of 0%

Wallonia-Brussels Federation

Controller of Commitments

Brussels (Belgium) July 2012 to June 2018

The French-speaking Community / Wallonia-Brussels Federation exercises its competencies in the French language region of Belgium and in regard to the institutions that fall under its purview in the bilingual Brussels-Capital Region.

- Effective task prioritization to meet tight deadlines under pressure
- Worked as part of a team of 4 controllers to control subsidies and public contracts for the whole Federation
- Implemented unique procedure for different functional departments to harmonize control operations
- Guided accountants for their budget requirements
- Inspected public contracts and subsidies before charging the budget for a total of 8 billion euros per year

Projects

Spotify-Lyrics Apr. 2019 to May 2019

A full stack web app built with **React, Redux and Express.** It connects to the Spotify API and to API Seeds Lyrics to automatically get the information and the lyrics of the track currently being played on the user's Spotify account.

Tinee Nov. 2018 to Dec. 2018

URL shortener built with **Mongo**, **Express**, **React** and **Node**. The basic functionality of shortening links and copying them is available to unauthenticated users. Logged-in users have their shortened links automatically saved.

InForm Sept. 2018 to Oct. 2018

Full stack web app built with **Node, Express, PostgreSQL** and **React**, InForm is a Form Building and Document Management system for trades companies. Users can build customised forms for staff to fill out, and once they've been submitted, Foremen and Managers can easily access those forms and stay up to date.

ChattyApp Sept. 2018 to Sept. 2018

A full stack chat web app built with **Node, Express** and **React**. It allows users to communicate in real time, recognizes image urls in messages and displays them as images.